2700chess.com 2019-07-08

# Privacy Policy - 2700chess.com

Last updated: June 13, 2018

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service (the "Service") at https://2700chess.com.

Your privacy is important for 2700chess.com and we will not use or share your information with anyone.

We use the HTTPS protocol. All web traffic between your web browser and https://2700chess.com uses the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) – in other words it is encrypted. Now, if anyone manages to intercept the message, all they will see is unintelligible text. 

We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at https://2700chess.com.

### Information Collection And Use

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your email address ("Personal Information").

### Log Data

We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third-party services, such as Google Analytics, that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Service's functionality.

These third-parties may use cookies to help us analyze how our users are using the Service and they have their own Privacy Policies addressing how they use such information.

### GDPR (General Data Protection Regulations)

Legal bases for processing (for EEA users) are as follows: If you are an individual in the European Economic Area (EEA), we collect and process information about you only where we have legal bases for doing so under applicable EU laws. The legal bases depend on theServices you use and how you use them. This means we collect and use your informationonly where:

— We need it to provide you the Services, including to operate the Services, provide customer support and personalized features and to protect the safety and security of the Services; 

— It satisfies a legitimate interest (which is not overridden by your data protection interests), such as for research and development, to market and promote the Services. 

We keep only your username, email and the public username you provided to 2700chess. Your password is encrypted so that we cannot see it.

### Deleting an account

If you want your account and associated data deleted, then please send us an email with a request to do so. We will then implement your request soon afterwards.

### Google Analytics

Google Analytics service is provided by Google Inc.

You can opt-out from Google Analytics service from using your information by installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser tool: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/

### Cookies

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

### Advertisements

The Service may have advertisements that are served by third-party service providers. These third-parties may collect and use information about you, including OS version, browser type, browser version, and other type of information, to show advertising of interest to you.

These third-parties may also collect information regarding the performance of the advertisements they provide, such as how many times an advertisement is shown, the number of click-throughs of an advertisement, and so on.

You can opt-out of interest-based advertisements served by these third-parties by following the instructions below. When you opt-out, you'll still see advertisements, but they may be less relevant because they aren't based on your interests.

### Google and the DoubleClick Cookie

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Service. Google's use of the DoubleClick Cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our Service or other web sites on the Internet.

You may opt-out of the use of the DoubleClick Cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the Google Ads Settings web page: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/

### Service Providers

We may employ third-party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

### Communications

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.

### Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### International Transfer

Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

### Links To Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that third-party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third-party sites or services.

### Children's Privacy

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from a children under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will take steps to remove that information from our servers.

### Changes To This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us. info(at)2700chess.com
